const quizData = [
{
    "question": "261. What is the output of the following Java code?",
    "code": "long value = 95;\nvalue = value-- + --value - value++ + ++value;\nSystem.out.println(value);\n",
    "a": "94",
    "b": "95",
    "c": "93",
    "d": "96",
    "correct": "b"
},
{
    "question": "262. Given the code snippet:",
    "code": "byte num = 100;\nnum = (byte)(num++ + num-- - --num + ++num);\n",
    "a": "101",
    "b": "100",
    "c": "99",
    "d": "102",
    "correct": "b"
},
{
    "question": "263. What will be the value of `result` after executing the code below?",
    "code": "short result = 100;\nresult = (short)(result++ - --result + result-- - ++result);\n",
    "a": "99",
    "b": "98",
    "c": "97",
    "d": "101",
    "correct": "c"
},
{
    "question": "264. What is the output of the following Java code?",
    "code": "byte x = 40;\nbyte y = 8;\nbyte z = (byte)(x-- - --y + y++ - ++x);\nSystem.out.println(z);\n",
    "a": "30",
    "b": "29",
    "c": "28",
    "d": "31",
    "correct": "b"
},
{
    "question": "265. After executing the following code, what will be the value of `counter`?",
    "code": "short counter = 45;\ncounter = (short)(counter-- - --counter + ++counter - counter--);\n",
    "a": "44",
    "b": "45",
    "c": "46",
    "d": "43",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
    "question": "266. What will be the value of `value` after executing the code below?",
    "code": "long value = 100;\nvalue = value-- + --value - value++ + ++value;\n",
    "a": "99",
    "b": "100",
    "c": "98",
    "d": "101",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
    "question": "267. Given the code snippet:",
    "code": "float num = 32.5f;\nnum = num++ + num-- - --num + ++num;\n",
    "a": "33.5",
    "b": "32.5",
    "c": "31.5",
    "d": "34.5",
    "correct": "b"
},
{
    "question": "268. What will be the output of the following Java code?",
    "code": "double a = 100.5;\ndouble b = 30.5;\ndouble result = a++ - ++b - b-- + --a;\nSystem.out.println(result);\n",
    "a": "70.5",
    "b": "69.5",
    "c": "68.5",
    "d": "71.5",
    "correct": "b"
},
{
    "question": "269. After the code is executed, what will be the value of `x`?",
    "code": "float x = 110.7f;\nx = x-- - --x + ++x - x++;\n",
    "a": "109.7",
    "b": "110.7",
    "c": "108.7",
    "d": "111.7",
    "correct": "c"
},
{
    "question": "270. What is the output of the following Java code?",
    "code": "long value = 105;\nvalue = value-- + --value - value++ + ++value;\nSystem.out.println(value);\n",
    "a": "104",
    "b": "105",
    "c": "103",
    "d": "106",
    "correct": "b"
},
{
    "question": "271. Given the code snippet:",
    "code": "byte num = 110;\nnum = (byte)(num++ + num-- - --num + ++num);\n",
    "a": "111",
    "b": "110",
    "c": "109",
    "d": "112",
    "correct": "b"
},
{
    "question": "272. What will be the value of `result` after executing the code below?",
    "code": "double result = 110.5;\nresult = result++ - --result + result-- - ++result;\n",
    "a": "109.5",
    "b": "108.5",
    "c": "107.5",
    "d": "110.5",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
    "question": "273. What is the output of the following Java code?",
    "code": "byte x = 50;\nbyte y = 10;\nbyte z = (byte)(x-- - --y + y++ - ++x);\nSystem.out.println(z);\n",
    "a": "40",
    "b": "39",
    "c": "38",
    "d": "41",
    "correct": "b"
},
{
    "question": "274. After executing the following code, what will be the value of `counter`?",
    "code": "short counter = 55;\ncounter = (short)(counter-- - --counter + ++counter - counter--);\n",
    "a": "54",
    "b": "55",
    "c": "56",
    "d": "53",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
    "question": "275. What will be the value of `value` after executing the code below?",
    "code": "long value = 110;\nvalue = value-- + --value - value++ + ++value;\n",
    "a": "109",
    "b": "110",
    "c": "108",
    "d": "111",
    "correct": "a"
},
{
            "question": "276. Given the code snippet:",
            "code": "float num = 37.5f;\nnum = num++ + num-- - --num + ++num;\n",
            "a": "38.5",
            "b": "37.5",
            "c": "36.5",
            "d": "39.5",
            "correct": "b"
        },
        {
            "question": "277. What will be the output of the following Java code?",
            "code": "double a = 110.5;\ndouble b = 32.5;\ndouble result = a++ - ++b - b-- + --a;\nSystem.out.println(result);\n",
            "a": "77.5",
            "b": "76.5",
            "c": "75.5",
            "d": "78.5",
            "correct": "b"
        },
        {
            "question": "278. After the code is executed, what will be the value of `x`?",
            "code": "float x = 120.7f;\nx = x-- - --x + ++x - x++;\n",
            "a": "119.7",
            "b": "120.7",
            "c": "118.7",
            "d": "121.7",
            "correct": "c"
        },
        {
            "question": "279. What is the output of the following Java code?",
            "code": "long value = 115;\nvalue = value-- + --value - value++ + ++value;\nSystem.out.println(value);\n",
            "a": "114",
            "b": "115",
            "c": "113",
            "d": "116",
            "correct": "b"
        },
        {
            "question": "280. Given the code snippet:",
            "code": "byte num = 120;\nnum = (byte)(num++ + num-- - --num + ++num);\n",
            "a": "121",
            "b": "120",
            "c": "119",
            "d": "122",
            "correct": "b"
        },
        {
            "question": "281. What will be the value of `result` after executing the code below?",
            "code": "double result = 120.5;\nresult = result++ - --result + result-- - ++result;\n",
            "a": "119.5",
            "b": "118.5",
            "c": "117.5",
            "d": "121.5",
            "correct": "c"
        },
        {
            "question": "282. What is the output of the following Java code?",
            "code": "byte x = 60;\nbyte y = 10;\nbyte z = (byte)(x-- - --y + y++ - ++x);\nSystem.out.println(z);\n",
            "a": "49",
            "b": "48",
            "c": "47",
            "d": "50",
            "correct": "b"
        },
        {
            "question": "283. After executing the following code, what will be the value of `counter`?",
            "code": "short counter = 65;\ncounter = (short)(counter-- - --counter + ++counter - counter--);\n",
            "a": "64",
            "b": "65",
            "c": "66",
            "d": "63",
            "correct": "a"
        },
        {
            "question": "284. What will be the value of `value` after executing the code below?",
            "code": "long value = 120;\nvalue = value-- + --value - value++ + ++value;\n",
            "a": "119",
            "b": "120",
            "c": "118",
            "d": "121",
            "correct": "a"
        },
        {
            "question": "285. Given the code snippet:",
            "code": "float num = 42.5f;\nnum = num++ + num-- - --num + ++num;\n",
            "a": "43.5",
            "b": "42.5",
            "c": "41.5",
            "d": "44.5",
            "correct": "b"
        },
        {
            "question": "286. What will be the output of the following Java code?",
            "code": "double a = 120.5;\ndouble b = 36.5;\ndouble result = a++ - ++b - b-- + --a;\nSystem.out.println(result);\n",
            "a": "83.5",
            "b": "82.5",
            "c": "81.5",
            "d": "84.5",
            "correct": "b"
        },
        {
            "question": "287. After the code is executed, what will be the value of `x`?",
            "code": "float x = 130.7f;\nx = x-- - --x + ++x - x++;\n",
            "a": "129.7",
            "b": "130.7",
            "c": "128.7",
            "d": "131.7",
            "correct": "c"
        },
        {
            "question": "288. What is the output of the following Java code?",
            "code": "long value = 125;\nvalue = value-- + --value - value++ + ++value;\nSystem.out.println(value);\n",
            "a": "124",
            "b": "125",
            "c": "123",
            "d": "126",
            "correct": "b"
        },
        {
            "question": "289. Given the code snippet:",
            "code": "byte num = 130;\nnum = (byte)(num++ + num-- - --num + ++num);\n",
            "a": "131",
            "b": "130",
            "c": "129",
            "d": "132",
            "correct": "b"
        },
        {
            "question": "290. What will be the value of `result` after executing the code below?",
            "code": "double result = 130.5;\nresult = result++ - --result + result-- - ++result;\n",
            "a": "129.5",
            "b": "128.5",
            "c": "127.5",
            "d": "131.5",
            "correct": "c"
        },
    ];
    
    


    const quiz = document.getElementById('quiz');
    const answerEls = document.querySelectorAll('.answer');
    const questionEl = document.getElementById('question');
    const codeEl = document.getElementById('code');
    const a_text = document.getElementById('a_text');
    const b_text = document.getElementById('b_text');
    const c_text = document.getElementById('c_text');
    const d_text = document.getElementById('d_text');
    const submitBtn = document.getElementById('submit');
    
    let currentQuiz = 0;
    let score = 0;
    let selectedAnswers = [];
    
    loadQuiz();
    
    function loadQuiz() {
        deselectAnswers();
    
        const currentQuizData = quizData[currentQuiz];
    
        questionEl.innerText = currentQuizData.question;
        codeEl.innerHTML = `<pre><code class="language-java">${currentQuizData.code}</code></pre>`;
        a_text.innerHTML = currentQuizData.a;
        b_text.innerHTML = currentQuizData.b;
        c_text.innerHTML = currentQuizData.c;
        d_text.innerHTML = currentQuizData.d;
    
        hljs.highlightAll(); // Apply syntax highlighting
    }
    
    function deselectAnswers() {
        answerEls.forEach(answerEl => answerEl.checked = false);
    }
    
    function getSelected() {
        let answer;
    
        answerEls.forEach(answerEl => {
            if (answerEl.checked) {
                answer = answerEl.id;
            }
        });
    
        return answer;
    }
    
    submitBtn.addEventListener('click', () => {
        const answer = getSelected();
    
        if (answer) {
            const currentQuizData = quizData[currentQuiz];
            const correctAnswerText = document.getElementById(currentQuizData.correct + "_text").innerText;
            const selectedAnswerText = document.getElementById(answer + "_text").innerText;
    
            if (answer === currentQuizData.correct) {
                score++;
                alert(`Correct! You selected "${selectedAnswerText}".`);
            } else {
                alert(`Incorrect! You selected "${selectedAnswerText}". The correct answer is "${correctAnswerText}".`);
            }
    
            selectedAnswers.push({
                question: currentQuizData.question,
                code: currentQuizData.code,
                selected: selectedAnswerText,
                correct: correctAnswerText,
                isCorrect: answer === currentQuizData.correct
            });
    
            currentQuiz++;
    
            if (currentQuiz < quizData.length) {
                loadQuiz();
            } else {
                showResults();
            }
        } else {
            alert("Please select an answer!");
        }
    });
    
    function showResults() {
        quiz.innerHTML = `
            <h2 style="text-align: center; font-size: 2rem;">Quiz Results</h2>
            <p style="font-size: 1.5rem; text-align: center;">You answered ${score}/${quizData.length} questions correctly</p>
            <div style="margin-top: 2rem; max-height: 400px; overflow-y: auto; padding: 1rem; border: 1px solid #ccc; border-radius: 10px;">
                <h3 style="text-align: center; margin-bottom: 2rem;">Detailed Summary</h3>
                <ul style="list-style-type: none; padding: 0; font-size: 1.2rem;">
                    ${selectedAnswers.map((result, index) => `
                        <li style="margin-bottom: 1.5rem;">
                            <strong>Question ${index + 1}:</strong> ${result.question}<br>
                            <pre><code class="language-java">${result.code}</code></pre>
                            <strong>Your Answer:</strong> ${result.selected} (${result.isCorrect ? '<span style="color: green;">Correct</span>' : '<span style="color: red;">Incorrect</span>'})<br>
                            ${!result.isCorrect ? `<strong>Correct Answer:</strong> ${result.correct}` : ''}
                        </li>
                    `).join('')}
                </ul>
            </div>
            <div style="text-align: center; margin-top: 2rem;">
                <button onclick="location.reload()" style="font-size: 1.2rem; padding: 0.8rem 1.5rem; background-color: #8e44ad; color: #fff; border: none; cursor: pointer;">Reload Quiz</button>
            </div>
        `;
    
        hljs.highlightAll(); // Apply syntax highlighting in the summary
    }
    